alert("hi");


$("#start").on("click", function() {
    game.start();

})

$(document).on("click","#end", function() {
    game.done();
  })
// Question set
var questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }, {
    question: "What movie won the oscar in 2017?",
    answers: ["Arrival", "Monlight", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }, {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story",
  }, {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }, {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }, {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }, {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }, {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }, {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }, {
    question: "What is the first full length CGI movie?",
    answers: ["A bug's Life", "Monster Inc.", "Toy Story", "The Lion King"],
    correctAnswer: "Toy Story"
  }];

// Variable that will hold the setInterval
var game = {

     correct: 0,
     incorrect: 0,
     counter: 60,

    countdown: function() {
        game.counter--;
        $("#counter").html(game.counter);
        if (game.counter <= 0) {
            game.done();
        }
    },
    
    start: function() {
      timer = setInterval(game.countdown, 1000);
      $("#sub-wrapper").prepend("<h2>Time Remaining: <span id="counter"> 60</span> Seconds</h2>");
      $("#start").remove();
          for (var i = 0; i < questions.length; i++) {
              $("#sub-wrapper").append("<h2>" + questions[1].questions+"</h2>");
              for (var j = 0; j < questions[1].answers.length; j++) {
                  $("#sub-wrapper").append("input type = "radio" name = questions-"+i+" value =""+questions[i].answers[j]+"">"+questions[i].answers[j]);
              }
          }
      $("#sub-wrapper").append("<button id="end">Done</button>");
    },
      // done button for each questions
    done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-0"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[0].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });

      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-1"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[1].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });

      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-2"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[2].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });

      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-3"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[3].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });

      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-4"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[4].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });
      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-5"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[5].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });

      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-6"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[6].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });

      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-7"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[7].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });
      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-8"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[8].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });

      done: function() {
      $.each($("input[name="questions-9"]:checked"), function() {
        if ($(this).val()==questions[9].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        }else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      });

      this.results();

    },
        results: function() {
            clearInterval(timer);
            $("#sub-wrapper h2").remove();
            $("#sub-wrapper").html("<h2> All Done</h2>");
            $("#sub-wrapper").append("<h3> Correct Answer: "+this.correct+"</h3>");
            $("#sub-wrapper").append("<h3> InCorrect Answer: "+this.Incorrect+"</h3>");
            $("#sub-wrapper").append("<h3> Unanswered: "+(questions.length-(this.incorrect+this.correct))"</h3>");
        }

    };



